so i think people thought i was joking when i said hey that's just a line from the zionist playbook
but there's actually a zionist playbook it was published in 2009 to help people defend the
atrocities of israel and if you don't believe me you could just type in that title the israel
project and you could download the 116 page document it even has a table of contents rules
for effective communication glossary of words that work how to talk about palestine self-government
and prosperity isolating iran-backed hamas as an obstacle to peace israel's right to self-defense
and defensible borders do you ever wonder why everyone sounds the same when they're talking
about israel there's no second opinion it's because it's literally written out for them this is not
this is 18 chapters so here this one this is like one chapter one the 25 rules for effective
communication and the first point is it doesn't matter if you know you need to show the other
side you care so they're telling people to fake caring so persuadables don't won't care how much
you know until they know how much you care show empathy empathy for both sides so this is like a
tactic that they tell people to do it's weird they have to write it out so this was nice too things not
to say we are prepared to allow them to build don't use that don't use that we allow them to build even
though that's what they're doing they're saying don't using it don't use it try this one achieving
peaceful relations requires a leadership political business and military of both sides and so we asked
the palestinians stop using that language of incitement stop using the language of violence and
you know they're trying to turn it back on the palestine but this is this is a script so when i say
this is a zionist line or from the playbook because it literally is from the playbook and this is what
every probably reporter or anchor on tv has in front of them every congressman is probably giving
this when they you know get sworn in here's your copy of the uh israel's zionist playbook so this is
uh like amazing that this isn't like exposed yet but how can the current palestinian leadership
honestly say it will pursue peace when previous leaders rejected an offer you always hear that
what about the offers that were rejected it came from here this is like this is still chapter one i
thing page like whatever but how do i make peace with a government who wants me dead why are they
phrasing it like that you ever wonder why they phrase it like that because they're told to phrase
it like this is actually i heard peace morgan use one of these in his um in his um interview with sinek
and he said that's a weird way to phrase the question it's an unfair way to um to phrase the
question and this is why because he got it from the playbook it's right here these are the questions
you're gonna hear a lot time and time again because it is scripted for them